Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV: Office Files, 1975
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) Bureau of Transportation, Economics and Statistics (General), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Volumes of "Transport Economics" by the Bureau of Economics
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) Ex Parte Number 274 Sub Number 1 - Special Procedures for Proposed Railroad Abandonments, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte Number 293, Sub 4, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    "Acquisition of rail properties by profitable railroads in the region as proposed by the U.S. Railway Association." Service Date May 27, 1975
  - Government: Ex Parte Number 293 - Northeastern Railroad Investigation [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13a)
    Includes circulars and filings in re ICC decisions.
  - Government: Ex Parte Number 293 - Northeastern Railroad Investigation [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13b)
  - Government: National Mediation Board (General), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Correspondence in re funding, appropriations, and budget of NMB and NRAB.
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Public Law Board, Decisions on Procedural Questions, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Includes Awards from the Public Law Board.
  - Government: Motor Carriers (General), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Emergency Board Reports, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Government: National Mediation Board - Membership and Staff Appointments, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Government: Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Government: Amendments Regarding Individuals as Bargaining Agents, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Government: Appropriations, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Government: Lists of Carriers and Designated Officers to Handle Disputes, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Government: Monthly Reports on Status of Cases, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 605 - Awards [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 24a)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 605 - Awards [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 24b)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 605 - Awards (continued) [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 25a)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 605 - Awards (continued) [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 20, Folder 25b)
  - Government: Special Board of Adjustment Number 570 - Decisions and Certifications, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Government Arbitration Board 298, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Government: Special Board of Arbitration 797 - Award, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board (General), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Includes the National mediation Board's "Review and Analysis of Railroad Adjustment Board and Public Law Boards, December 31, 1974."
  - Government: NRAB First Division, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Government: NRAB Second Division, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Government: NRAB Third Division, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Government: NRAB Fourth Division, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Government: NRAB Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Government: NRAB Membership, National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Includes 40th Annual Report of the national Mediation Board.
  - Government: NRAB Application of Awards, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Party Notices, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Government: NRAB Membership and Staff Appointments, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board (General), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Reports for Railway Labor Executives Association (RLEA) Meeting from Railroad Board, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Includes quarterly financial reports, actuarial notices, and schedules of informational meetings. Also includes pamphlets on sickness and unemployment benefits for railroad employees.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices (Schedule of Regular Itinerant Service), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Mechanization and Centralization of Claims Payments, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board - Status of Funds Actuarial Reports, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Includes monthly benefit statements and Quarterly Financial Reports.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement, Benefits, and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Includes circulars and information on an increase in unemployment benefits.
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Annuities Affected by PL 91-588 (Veterans Pensions), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etcetera (Scheduled Informational Conference), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Press Releases, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans (Supplemental Pensions), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Government: Administration of Medicare - Financial Intermediary, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Government: Commission on Railroad Retirement, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    Includes newsletter and a certificate of membership for the RLEA.
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (AMTRAK), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    Includes papers and reports from "Symposium of Transportation Issues, September 17-19, 1975." Also includes newspaper clippings, correspondence in re passes, copies of the "Amtrak Blues" newsletter about issues with Amtrak by some of its employees, train schedules, and press releases.
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (C-2 Protective Agreement), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Government: President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Government: Civil Rights, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    Includes filings against carriers and railway labor unions for civil rights violations. Also includes circular in re the application of the SCOTUS decision on Albermarle Paper Co. V. Moody et al. on railroad labor unions.
  - Government: Fast Freight Systems Transportation Corporation (FASTCOR), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Government: Cost of Living Council, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Government: Regional Rail Reorganization Act of 1973 [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 36a)
    Includes documentation on the creation of ConRail under the Regional Rail Reorganization Act and the creation of employee protection agreements.
  - Government: Regional Rail Reorganization Act of 1973 [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 36b)
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 1, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    includes "Statement of the Penn Central Trustees on the United States Railway Association's Final System Plan" expressing their disapproval of the plan. Also includes correspondence and press releases.
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 2 [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 21, Folder 38a)
    Includes reports on preliminary and final system plans of the USRA, the report of the public counsel, and reports on Penn Central employees.
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 2 [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 21, Folder 38b)
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 3 [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    Includes Final System Plan and an analysis of the proposed amendments.
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 4, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    Includes various proposals for acquisition of Penn central trackage by other carriers. Proposals include maps of tracks and surrounding areas.
  - Government: United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 5, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Government. United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 6 [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2a)
    Includes RLEA circulars in re implementation of reorganization and employee protection agreements, newspaper clippings, and USRA system plans.
  - Government. United States Railway Association (Created by Regional Rail Reorganization Act) File 6 [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2b)
  - Government: CONRAIL (Consolidated Rail Corporation), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Includes Congressional report, "The Financial Viability of ConRail."
  - Government: CONRAIL (Consolidated Rail Corporation), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Bound volume, "Evaluation of the Final System Plan's Financial Analysis" by Alain Kornhauser.
  - Judicial: Court Cases (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Judicial: Penn Central Bankruptcy (Reorganization), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and newspaper clippings.
  - Judicial: Boston and Maine Reorganization, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Judicial: Lehigh Valley Reorganization, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Includes U.S. District Court's order for Lehigh Valley to continue operating its New England tracks.
  - Judicial: Reading Reorganization, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - judicial: Central Railroad of New Jersey Reorganization, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Judicial: Jacksonville Terminal (Civil Rights), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Judicial: Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Reorganization, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Judicial: Joel Anderson and Prince Edmonds et al versus Southern Pacific Transportation Company (Civil Rights), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: General [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14a)
    Includes letter announcing the re-unification of RLEA and CRU on April 1, 1975 and minutes of the meeting where the reunification was proposed and adopted by vote.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: General [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Miami Meeting, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Includes hotel brochures, attendance lists, planning documents, and correspondence.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Constitution and By-Laws, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Amendments to constitution in re reunification.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Officers and Members, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Updated list of names and titles in re reunification
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Bicentennial Celebrations (Planning), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Includes brochures from various Washington DC institutions in re their plans for the bicentennial.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Railroad Labor Executives Association: Railway Employees' Department - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    Includes arbitration award involving furlough of protected employees by the Penn Central Transportation Co.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    CRU/RLEA File.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    CRU/RLEA File. Correspondence file, including notice that BRAC disaffiliated from CRU and was not part of the reunification with RLEA.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Seafarers' International Union, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    CRU/RLEA File. No records contained in folder when collection accessioned.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Transport Workers Union of America, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: United Transportation Union, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    CRU/RLEA File. Includes UTU pamphlets: "How to protect your rights when injured in the job;" and "Transportation and Energy" by Al H. Chesser.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Miami Meeting, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    CRU File. Correspondence and hotel brochures.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Miami Meeting Agendas, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Meetings (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Reports of Counsel, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Agendas, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Assessments, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    Includes letter in re how reunification affects the assessments of member unions.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Applications for Affiliation, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Wages and Rules (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Radio Telephone Equipment Communications, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Florida East Coast Railway, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    Correspondence in re ongoing strike on FEC Railway.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedure, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1970 Wage Rules Movement, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1973 Wage Rules Movement, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1973 Guaranteed Annual Wage - Employment Security, Wages, Etcetera (Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1974 Wage Rules Movement, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    Includes circulars from Railway Employees' Department, AFL-CIO and the Report to the President by Emergency Board 187.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Health and Welfare [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 55a)
    In re Travelers' Insurance group policies, including GA23000.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Health and Welfare [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 55b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Traveler's Insurance Company, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Operating Unions, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Rules Committee, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Shop (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Dues (General), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Washington Job Protection Agreement [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1a)
    Includes filings in re Docket Nos. 172 and 173.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Washington Job Protection Agreement [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railway Labor Building, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committees (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Includes list of standing committees.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Safety Committee, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Includes bound materials
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etcetera, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads - Railroad Labor-Management Relations [folder 1 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7a)
    Includes minutes of monthly committee meetings, minutes of meeting of the Task Force on Rail Transportation, reports from the Council for a Sound Waterways Policy, newspaper clippings, and information on regulations on truck weight limits.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads - Railroad Labor-Management Relations [folder 2 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads - Railroad Labor-Management Relations [folder 3 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7c)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force: "The Truth About American Ground Transport", 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Bound volume. Published by General Motors.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force, Terminals [folder 1 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9a)
    Includes minutes of meeting, reports on Civil Rights in workplace agreements and seniority rosters, a report on Chicago Railroad Terminal Operations in 1974, and progress reports on experiments to improve operations in Chicago Terminals.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force, Terminals [folder 2 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Labor Management Task Force, Terminals [folder 3 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9c)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on the Council of Allied Labor (C.O.A.L.) Burlington Northern, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Passes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Personnel Records (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Prospective Employees (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Personal Property Tax, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: GPO Account 11256, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Government Printing Office? Found Empty October 28, 2014
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Insurance (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Postage Meter, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Office Equipment (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: The XEROX Copying Machine, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Office Furniture (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Registration for Lobbying, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers Bills [folder 1 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 31a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers Bills [folder 2 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 31b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers Bills [folder 3 of 3], 1975 (Box 23, Folder 31c)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Shop Crafts Dispute, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Contracting Out (General), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Railroads: General, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Railroads: Ownership, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Railroads: Penn Central, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Railroads: Illinois Railroad, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Railroads: Auto-Train Corporation, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6a)
    Newsletters
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6b)
  - Railroads: Western Railroad Association, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees (General), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations - Medicare, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (General) [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 12a)
    Includes newsletters, resolutions, press releases, and a course catalog for the labor studies center.
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (General) [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 12b)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Civil Rights Department, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO - Minutes, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO - Legislative Newsletter, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Council, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)